<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Site</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Personal Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenFAAS via Faasd and Terraform on Openstack</title>
      <link>/posts/openfaas-openstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/openfaas-openstack/</guid>
      <description>Intro OpenFAAS is a serverless tool. One of the things I like most about it - it&amp;rsquo;s pretty agnostic. You can bring your own infra or orchestrator and roll with Dockerfiles (as long as they conform to the OpenFaas serverless workload definition). No vendor lock in!
Their tagline: OpenFaaS® makes it simple to deploy both functions and existing code to Kubernetes
While OpenFaas is mainly used with k8s, there are other providers available too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>k3s, Ubuntu 19.10 and a Pi4</title>
      <link>/posts/ubuntu-pi4-k3s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ubuntu-pi4-k3s/</guid>
      <description>On the matter of Operating Systems Raspian is perfectly good, but there are a few niggles. It isn&amp;rsquo;t 64 bit, so running things like mongodb is a problem. Also, it&amp;rsquo;d be nice to use cloud-init to preconfigure some stuff, such as SSH keys. If you want to try a 64 bit OS for your Pi4, Ubuntu is a solid option.
cgroup_memory = 0 cgroup_memory is disabled by default on raspbian and is required for k8s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenFAAS via Containerd on a Raspberry PI 4</title>
      <link>/posts/pi4-containerd-openfaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/pi4-containerd-openfaas/</guid>
      <description>Intro OpenFAAS is a serverless tool. One of the things I like most about it - it&amp;rsquo;s pretty agnostic. You can bring your own infra or orchestrator and roll with Dockerfiles. No vendor lock in!
Their tagline: OpenFaaS® makes it simple to deploy both functions and existing code to Kubernetes
While it is mainly used with k8s, there are also providers for other orchestrators, such as Hashicorp&amp;rsquo;s Nomad. Today I&amp;rsquo;ll be trying out a new provider for Containerd on my Raspberry Pi 4b.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 11:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>wotcha Research Computing Specialist @ the University of Cambridge.
Talk to me about: * Orchestraion: Terraform, K8s, Nomad * CfgMgt: Ansible * CNCF tooling</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Hugo Site</title>
      <link>/posts/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/home/</guid>
      <description>First post on the new site. It&amp;rsquo;s a hugo site, using the terminal theme by panr. Previously Pelican was my static site generator of choice but I&amp;rsquo;ve heard good things about Hugo and fancied giving it a go.
Here&amp;rsquo;s how its configured:
Installation I&amp;rsquo;m using Hugo with Github Pages) and my own hosting.
As I won&amp;rsquo;t be using Hugo/this blog everyday I will forget the commands for it so I&amp;rsquo;ve wrapped everything I need into a Makefile:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>